Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII: Welfare Department. Papers, 1940-1975
  - Sub-Series A. General, 1940-1968
    - Community Services, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 31-34)
      Minutes, notices of meetings, lists of counselors, etc.
    - Consumer Service Material, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 35)
      Pamphlets with consumer interest material
    - D - General correspondence, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - D - Worker correspondence, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Disability Claims, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 38-46)
      Rejections, correspondence
    - E - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 47)
    - Employers Council & Local 64, Trust Fund Reports, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 48)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 49)
    - F - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 50)
    - Forms, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 51)
      Missing information, medical claim forms
    - Fur Dressers & Dyers Pension & Retirement Fund, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 52)
      Minutes of trustee meetings
    - Fur Dressers & Dyers Welfare Fund, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 53)
    - Fur Joint Board, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 54-56)
      Independent employees group remittance reports
    - G - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - G - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
    - Group Health Association, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - H - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - H - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Health, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - HIP Employees listing, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - HIP General, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      Members handbook, correspondence, newsletters, annual report
    - Hospital Service Plan - Fur Dressers & Dyers Welfare Plan, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 10-11)
    - Hospital Service Plan - Lehigh Valley, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Hospital Service Plan - New Jersey, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Housing, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 14-16)
      Information on tenants rights, applications for housing
    - I - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - J - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Joint Board 25th Anniversary Conference, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 20-21)
      October 5, 1963. Reports, prep material, speeches, financial information
    - Joint Board Newsletter, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Joint Board Welfare & Retirement Fund, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 23)
      financial information
    - K - Workers Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - L - Workers Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Empty file folder (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Legislation, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 28)
      King Anderson Bill, health card, etc. Letters urging members to support
    - List of members, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - M - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - M - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 31-33)
    - Major Medical Information, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 34)
      Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance information
    - Meeting notices, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Minutes - Retirement Center meetings, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 36)
    - Minutes - Welfare Fund, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 38-40)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 41)
    - N - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 42)
    - O - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 43)
    - O - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 44)
    - P - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 45-47)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund - Fur Dresser & Dyers Union, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 48-49)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund - Local 64, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 50-53)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund, Local 85, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund, Local 150, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 55)
    - Photos - Negatives, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 56)
    - Q - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 57)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 58)
    - R - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 59-60)
    - Radio City Tours, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Reports - Welfare & Retirement, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Retirement Center Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 3-4)
    - Retirement Center Films - lists, plans for films, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Retirement Center - material on aging, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 6-7)
    - Retirement Center, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      Trip to UN, includes photos of getting on bus and at the UN
    - Retirement Center - Notices of meeting, minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - S - General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - S - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Social Security Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      letters from above re surveys being conducted
    - T - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - U - General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - U - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      pamphlets, letter from Cammer & Shapiro re new amendments concerning above
    - United Medical Service - newsletters, pamphlets, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - V - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - W - General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - W - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Welfare Fund - Fur Dressers & Dyers, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Welfare Fund, Local 64, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Welfare Fund, Local 85, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Welfare Fund, Local 150, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Welfare & Pension Fund material, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 25-26)
      various brochures, newsletters, etc.
    - Workman's Compensation, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - XYZ - Worker Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, (all) groups of shops, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B-C, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, Herman Basch & Co., 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-H, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-O, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - New York Attachment Corp., 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 35)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 36)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Trubitz Hardware, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 38)
    - A - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 39)
    - A - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 40)
    - Address plate Corp., 1964 (Box 95, Folder 41)
    - AMC&BW of NA - Chicago, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 42)
    - Associated Hospital Service - information on health industry, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 43-44)
    - Associated Hospital Service - report, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 45)
    - Associated Optometrists - contract, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 46)
    - Association of Health, Welfare & Pension Plan Administrators, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 47-48)
      newsletters and pamphlets
    - B - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 49)
    - B - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
    - C - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - C - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 4-5)
    - Camp, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Community Services - general information, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 8-9)
    - Community Services - minutes of committee meetings, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - D - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Death Notices, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Disability Claims Rejected, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - E - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      Employer contributions - dues, insurance & retirement
    - Fur Dressers & Dyers Fund, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Local 64, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 18-20)
    - Local 88, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Local 150, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - F - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Feliciano, Salvatore - welfare case, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Financial Statements, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Forms - various welfare, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Fur Joint Board, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 28-30)
      lists of independent employees and their group insurance info
    - Fur Merchants Employer Council - insurance information, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - G - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - G - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 33-35)
    - Grand Opticians, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - H - General, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - H - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - HIP - premium statements, Local 64, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 39-41)
    - Hospital Service Plan - Lehigh Valley, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - Hospital Service Plan - New Jersey, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 43-44)
    - Housing, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 45-47)
      tenant news, rights, information on housing, metropolitan housing meetings, flyers, etc.
    - I - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - Inter-office memos, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - J - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - Joint Board Welfare Fund Financial Information, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - K - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 53)
    - K - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 54-55)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 56)
    - L - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
    - Labor, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      newsletters, information from NYS Department of Labor
    - Leaflets - strike support, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      letters to and from Senators re medical cases, Medicare support, etc.
    - M - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - M - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 7-9)
    - Master List of employees in health care plan, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers - Insurance & Retirement, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - N - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - O - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - P - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      including photographs of David Cleiman - father of the year
    - P - Worker Correspondence, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 17-18)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund Information, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 19-24)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund information, Local 64, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 25-32)
    - R&J Tanning - worker's compensation claims, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - Rehabilitation, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 34)
      labor rehabilitation liaison project in New York City
    - Retirement Center Material, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 33-36)
    - Shapiro & Sons - insurance material, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Shops - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 38-40)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Maspeth Tannings, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 41)
    - Associated Hospital Service of NY, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 42-43)
      group account statements
    - Association of Health, Welfare & Pension Plan Administrators, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 44-46)
      minutes of meetings, notices & newsletters
    - Birth Control - Planned Parenthood information, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 47)
    - Community Services, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 48)
      minutes of Community Services counsellors, meeting, routine
    - Entertainers - brochures to Germaine Wasserman, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 49)
    - Health - general, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 50)
    - HIP - Fur Joint Board - premium statements, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 51)
    - HIP - Fur Merchants employees premium statements, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 52)
    - Investments, Local 150, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Legislation (Federal), AFL-CIO Legislative Report, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Hart Bill, congressional correspondence
    - Medical-Surgical Plan of NJ, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund information, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 4-6)
      Fur Dressers & Dyers
    - Pension & Retirement Fund information, Local 64, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 7-8)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund information, Local 150, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
    - Retirees Voice, newsletter, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Retirement Center - activities, plans, info, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - State Legislature - NYS AFL-CIO, legislative report, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Welfare & Retirement Fund - Joint Board, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 14-15)
    - A - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - A - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Associated Hospital Service, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - B - General, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Empty file folder, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - B - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 21-23)
    - Blood Bank, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 24-26)
    - Blue Cross Bank, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 27-28)
    - Bowling Team, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Booklets, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - C - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 31)
    - C - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 32-33)
    - Camp Applications, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 34)
    - Chiropractors, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 35)
    - Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 36)
    - Community Services Committee, Fur Joint Board, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 37)
      meeting notices
    - Community Services Committee - general, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 38)
    - Community Services News, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 39)
    - D - General, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 40)
    - D - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 41-42)
    - Death Notices, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 43)
    - Dental, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 44)
    - Disability claims rejected, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 45)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 46)
    - E - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 47)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 48)
    - F - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 49-50)
    - Form Letters, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 51)
    - Free Lance Fur Assorters, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 52)
    - Fur Dressers & Dyers Welfare Fund, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 53)
    - Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 54)
    - Furriers Supply Merchants Assn., 1966 (Box 98, Folder 55)
    - G - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 56)
    - G - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 57-59)
    - Group Health newsletters, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 60-61)
    - H - General, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 62)
    - H - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 63)
    - Health Insurance Plan, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 64)
    - Health Insurance Reports, Premium Statement, Local 64, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 1-5)
    - Health Welfare & Pension Plans, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      National Foundation information
    - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - I - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Inter-Office correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Italian Flood Fund, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - J - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Joint Board - amended by-laws & constitution, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - K - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - K - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 15-16)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - L - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Leaflets, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Lehigh Valley Blue Cross, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - M - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - M - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 22-24)
    - Medicare, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Minutes of Meetings, Local 64 & Local 150 Pension and Retirement Funds, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Myerscough, Tom - Affair - Photos, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - N - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 30-31)
    - National Foundation of Health and Welfare Plans, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - News Releases, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - O - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - P - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - P - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 36-37)
    - Peace, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Fur Dressers & Dyers, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 39-40)
    - Local 64, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 41-43)
    - Local 160, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 44-45)
    - Political Action Committee, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 46)
    - Q - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 47)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 48)
    - R - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 49-52)
    - Rehabilitation, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 53)
    - Retirees Voice, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 54)
    - Retirement Activities Film, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 55)
    - Retirement Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 56-57)
    - Retirement - General, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 58-59)
    - Retirement Planning Committee, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 60)
    - S - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 61)
    - S - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 62-64)
    - Sample men, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 65)
    - Sewing Machine Industry, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 66)
    - Shop Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 67-70)
    - Shop Status Sheets (contributors), 1966 (Box 100, Folder 1-5)
    - Staff Meetings, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - T - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - T - Worker Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 8-9)
    - Taft Hartley, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Teachers Insurance Plan, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Textile Association of the Fur Industry, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Travel, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Unemployment Insurance, New York & New Jersey, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - U - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - U - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - United Mechanics 150 Welfare Fund, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - United Medical Service, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - U, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - W - General, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - W - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 21-22)
    - Ewin Wagner Testimonial Dinner, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - General Welfare & Pension Plans, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Joint Board, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Joint Council 3, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Workman's Compensation, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - X-Y-Z - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - X-Y-Z - Workers Correspondence, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 29)
    - A - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - A - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - AMC&BW of NA, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - Associated Hospital Service, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - Association of Health, Welfare & Pension Plans, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - B - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - B - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 36-39)
    - Blood Bank, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 40)
    - C - General, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 41)
    - C - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 42-43)
    - Cammer & Shapiro, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 44)
    - Camps, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 45)
    - Coren, John, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 46)
      miscellaneous file with newsletters from various community organizations - Black associations - school and youth committees
    - Children - Retarded, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 47)
    - Chiropractors, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 48)
    - C, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 49)
    - Community Services - general, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 50)
    - Community Services - meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 51)
    - Community Services Report, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 52)
    - Contract Clauses, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 53)
    - D - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 54)
    - D - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 55-56)
    - Death Notices, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 57)
    - Disability Benefits, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 58)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 59)
    - E - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 60)
    - Elections, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 61)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 62)
    - F - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 63)
    - Forms for benefits, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 64-65)
    - G - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 67-68)
    - Group Health, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 69)
    - H - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 70)
    - H - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 71-72)
    - HIP - Fur Joint Board, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 73-74)
    - HIP - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 75)
    - HIP Local 64, premium, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
    - Health, Welfare & Pension Plans, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Hospital Service Plan, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
    - Housing - Metropolitan Council, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 6-10)
    - I - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Inter-office memos, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Institute - Local 27, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - J - Workers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Joint Board, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 16)
      form letters, welfare policies, report to conference on welfare
    - Joint Board newsletters, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Joint Board, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 18)
      Report on Welfare by Germaine Wasserman to Conference - 1/27/67
    - K - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - K - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 20-21)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - L - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 23-24)
    - Labor - Dept. of Labor reports, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Local 27, notice of meetings, reports, etc., 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - M - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - M - Worker Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 28-30)
    - Medicaid, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 31-35)
      newsletter, information about Medicaid correspondence with union
    - Medical Surgical Plan of New Jersey, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - Medicare - General information and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Mental Health reports - general, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous - list of names (receiving benefits with ID's), 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 40-43)
    - Mutual of Omaha, routine, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund Information, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 45-46)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund, Local 64, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 47)
    - Pension & Retirement Fund, Local 150, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 48)
    - Welfare & Pension Plans - General, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 49)
    - Welfare & Pension Plans - Joint Board, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 50)
    - Welfare & Pension Plans - Joint Council 3, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 51)
    - A - Worker Correspondence, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 52)